If you want to go to Vegas and make some money at the crap table.
My name is Dean Hale and I'm going to teach you how to win at craps.
Craps is a game where if you roll as the shooter comes out and shoots and he rolls a seven or eleven you win.
But there's also other ways to win at craps.
There's a pass line, and if you put the money on the pass line and the shooter rolls a seven or an eleven, you win automatically.
Unfortunately if they roll two, three or twelve you lose.
Now what you are going to want to do is the safest way to hedge your bet in craps is to try to have your money on three different numbers.
So what you are going to do is you are going to put money down on the pass line, and if they roll a seven or eleven great you win.
Take the money off and you can bet again.
If they don't and they hit their point or say they roll an eight and that's their point, you want to put some money on the come out line.
So that's going to give you a better chance to hedge your bet.
What you are going to want to do is eventually have money on three different numbers.
This takes down the casino advantage to it's lowest point.
That's the easiest way to try to win some money at craps, is to minimize the casino's advantage.
So pass line, if they don't hit their seven eleven initially, try to get it on the come out line, your money on two different numbers so you can minimize the casino's advantage.
My name is Dean Hale and I've just given you the best advice you can get about winning at craps.